wherevent.com 2011-03-04

# Wherevent.com

### Personnal data

WHEREVENT may need to gather personal information. WHEREVENT uses the term “personal information” to mean any information disclosed by Users – as natural persons – of whatever nature, such as their names, forenames, addresses, third party Id, e-mail and passwords, and which enables them to be identified directly or otherwise, whether such information is provided voluntarily by Users or collected in the context of browsing the Site. Personal information gathered about Users is intended for use by WHEREVENT. Such information may be copied, used and/or stored, and may not be disclosed to third parties except if specifically required by law or by any judicial authority. All Users may exercise their right to access, rectify and delete data concerning them by sending their request by email to: contact@wherevent.com WHEREVENT collects, processes and uses personal data in compliance with the privacy laws of France and the privacy terms of the European Union. 

### Third party data

WHEREVENT collects data about public third party events. The collect will concern third party events that users or their third party contacts are related to. These data can be gather online (by using users third party session while users are connected to WHEREVENT) or offline (by using users third party token session while users are not connected to WHEREVENT). WHEREVENT may store these data in a database in order to feed the service with third party public events. No private events will be collected by WHEREVENT. However WHEREVENT won't be held responsible if ,accidentaly or after an update of a third party event previously collected by WHEREVENT, some private third party are store in the WHEREVENT database. If this happens all users can contact WHEREVENT by sending their request by email to: contact@wherevent.com in order to rectify or delete data concerning a private third party event store by WHEREVENT. 

### Events

WHEREVENT offers you the possibility to invite people to parties, meetings and events. You can invite WHEREVENT members as well as non-members to the events. WHEREVENT show details about Events such as Picture, description, comments, attendees people, third party friends attending. 

### Email

Why did you receive an email from WHEREVENT? If you received a mailing from WHEREVENT, your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. How WHEREVENT protect your privacy WHEREVENT use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. Sharing and Usage WHEREVENT will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to WHEREVENT is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. How can you stop receiving email from WHEREVENT? If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent by WHEREVENT, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to contact@wherevent.com for review.
